<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168645</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, Second Year Class, 1948-1949</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Holsinger's Studio (Charlottesville, Va.)</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1948/1949</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>First row (l to r): George Byron Alder, Albert Harold Arenowitz, Evan Hamilton Ashby, Jr.,
Ratcliffe Cox Barnes, Wayland Richard Bennett, Frank Nash Bilisoly, III, Lewis Booker, Harvey Jerome
Breit, Seymour Brenner, Raymond Keith Brown, John Chalkey Buchanan. Second row (l to r): Ira
Marshall Cantin, Wallace Alexander Coburn, Charles Harper Crowder, Jr., William Templeton Davis,
Paul Sahak Derian, William Stribling Dingledine, Charles Coleman Donegan, Jr., Adolphe Max
Ehrenworth, Warren Dunlap Elliott, Kenneth Hall Epple, Clifford Henry Fox, John Breckenridge Gorman.
Third row (l to r): Anthony James Grieco, Francis Gordon Griffin, Robert Harris, Robert Traylor
Helmen, Philip Kearney Hensel, Durell Boyd Horsley, Austin Taber Hyde, Jr., Allan Hammett Jefferies,
James Edward John, Jr., Albert McCray Jones, Herbert Claiborne Jones, Jr. Fourth row (l to r):
Joseph Humphries Magee, James Dunn Mason, Jr., Billy Francis McGuire, Richard Bennett Meriwether,
Charles Samuel Miller, Andrew Christmond Mitchell, Charles Hunter Montgomery, Bernard Oseroff,
William Herman Pifer, Harry Hawthorne Robinson, Jr., Charles Henry Sackett, Robert Bailey Sandord,
Jr. Fifth row (l to r): Joseph Lee Sedwitz, Lewis Willard Shankel, William Henry Sipe, Philip George
Spaeth, Carl Ellroy Stark, John Miles Stirewalt, Edward Jordan Stoll, James Walter Stone, William
Harold Stout, Albert Isadore Strauss, Henry Morse Tanner, Jr. Sixth row (l to r): Richard Norvell
Taylor, William Taylor Tucker, Moffett Robson Walker, William Puller Wharton, James David Wilson,
Thomas Mahlon Wright, Harry Robert Yates, Jr.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168645/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168645</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168645/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
