<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168672</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, Fourth Year Class, 1957</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Thompson, Ralph R.</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1957</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>First row (l to r): Noel Martin Rowan, Charles Baynham Mahon, James Trigg Gillespie, John
Iverson Boswell, William Swadley Erwin, Jr., Henry Wayne Poore, Julian Arthur Koplen, Robert Lee
Glenn, Marvin Miles Sager, Faith Hilda Kung, Francis Edwards Rushton, James Robert Hicks II, John
Roger Casey, William Thomas Carter, Edgar Clifford Lawson, Charles Richard Chamberlain, Jr. Second
row (l to r): John Loomis Chamberlain III, Warren Woodson Koontz, Jr., Alexander Farish Robertson
III, Mark Henderson Congdon, Edward Joseph Armbruster, Robert Walter Olwine, Julius Conn, Jr., Peter
Van Cortlandt Moore, Edward Thomas Wood, David L. Lewis, Loyd Clarence Brannon, George Bluford Naff,
John Orton Shaw, Tureman Gayle Weaver. Third row (l to r): William Carter Lowe, George Allan Ferre,
Martin Perlman William Lloyd Meehan, Howard Nan Stewart, Robert Barksdale Ooghe, Allan Lee Drash,
Wilford Wayne Spradlin, Frederick Carr Davis, Jr., Leif Oscar Torkelson, Phillip Morton Levy, Macon
Smiley Couk, William Sidney Foreman, Jr., James Hawver McVey, John Jefferson Lund. Fourth row (l to
r): Howard Mortye Vinecour, Charles Henry Gleason, Jess Peck Piller, Donald Raymond Cagle, Robert
Francis Baxter, Charles Penick Olinger, Edward Bertram Nash, Cyrus Patrick Lewis, Gwendolyn Rosalie
Hogan, John Wesley Emerick, Jr., Theron Rice Rolston, Jr., Haakon Ragde, Edmund Roland Weise, Joseph
Hodges Fitzgerald, William Mayo Oppenheimer, William Turkington Clarke. Fifth row (l to r): Bruce
Alexander Talmadge, Stuart Horsley Harris, Jr., John Robert Talbert, George Walker Sommers, Jr.,
James Edwin Patterson, Hugh Richard Howell, Luke Combs, Joseph Emory Coleman, Hobart Garfield
Hansen, Jr., Lockhart Bemiss McGuire, Edward Joseph Sheridan, Jr., Charles Reames Young, James
Parker Cross, Jr., George Ely Walker.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168672/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168672</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168672/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
