<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168539</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>Fourth Year Class, 1929-1930</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Holsinger's Studio (Charlottesville, Va.)</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1929/1930</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>SOM, Class of 1930 Identified, from left to right: Top row: Richard F. Slaughter Jr., Robert
E. Odom, William O. Purdy, Archibald A. Little Jr., Achilles L. Tynes Jr., Lewis B. Sheppard,
Frederick M. Morrison, William M. Gammon, Harold H. McLemore, J. R. Eggleston, Thomas L. Watson Jr.,
Dorothy D. Brame, Daniel B. Pierson Jr., William H. Paine Jr. Second row: Beverly K. Peter, Ernest
S. Elliott, Henry R. Bourne, Oliver L. Von Canon, Benjamin W. Rawles Jr., James E. Wissler, Richard
E. White, H. T. Marshall (Pathology and Bacteriology), Paul H. Revercomb, Julian E. West, Thomas L.
Allman, Prosser H. Picot, William C. Wills, Charles Keppler Jr., Charles B. Smith Third row: Robert
L. Wells, Paul S. Hill, Eugune B. Ferris Jr., George T. Gwathmey Jr., J. A. Waddell (Materia-Medica
and Pharmacology), H. E. Jordan (Histology and Embryology), [skip center photo], E. P. Lehman
(Surgery and Gynecology), J. E. Kindred (Histology and Embryology), John D. Peake, Charles W.
Rodgers, Hill Carter III, William H. Roper Fourth row: Southgate Leigh Jr., Paul Kells, Edward S.
Orgain, H. B. Mulholland (Medicine), W. E. Brown (Phthisiotherapy), [skip center photo], J. H. Neff
(Urology), D. C. Smith (Dermatology and Syphilology), Alfred C. Ray Jr., William L. Sibley, Emory L.
Shiflett Center photo: Dr. J. C. Flippin - Dean Fifth row: William A. Brumfield Jr., Joseph H.
Farrow, Joel L. Deuterman, James E. Amiss, V. W. Archer (Roentgenology), W. E. Bray (Clincal
Diagnosis), H. S. Hedges (Ophthalmology), L. T. Royster (Pediatrics), W. H. Goodwin (Surgery), K. F.
Maxcy (Health and Hygiene), John C. Palmer, Walter J. Allegree, Dewey L. Anderson, Morton M.
Pinckney Sixth row: Alexander T. Mayo, Bergliot Stromsoe, Allan E. Walker Jr., C. C. Speidel
(Anatomy), L. A. Calkins (Gynecology and Obstetrics), J. E. Wood (Medicine), A. F. Voshell
(Orthopedics), R. B. Bean (Anatomy), F. D. Woodward (Otolaryngology ), F. B. Carter (Obstetrics), S.
D. Blackford (Medicine), James P. King, Manfred Call III, Robert B. Skinner Seventh row: Alfred W.
Pinkerton, D. C. Wilson (Psychiatry-Neurology), A. D. Hart (Medicine), O. Swineford (Medicine), T.
F. Brumfield (Bacteriology and Pathology), H. W. Smith (Physiology), F. B. Stafford
(Phthisotherapy), E. S. Sanderson (Pathology and Bacteriology), R. M. Meade (Surgery), W. W. Waddell
(Pediatrics), C. B. Morton (Surgery), A. Chanutin (Biochemistry), R. T. Ergenbright (Orthopedics),
Joseph P. Coco</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168539/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168539</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168539/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
