<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168547</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, Second Year Class, 1930-1931</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Holsinger's Studio (Charlottesville, Va.)</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1930/1931</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>Class of 1933 Identified (L to R): First row: Charles Jefferson Albright, Charles Varner
Amole, Edwin Edmunds Barksdale, Nathaniel Lewis Bosworth, Jr., Hugh Roland Butt, William Bernard
Carpenter, Charles Henry Conley, Jr., Cesare Frances DeBiase, John Essary Dees, Clayton Bernard
Ethridge, Glassell Slaughter Fitz-Hugh, Harrison Fitzgerald Flippin, Edgar Coley Garrard, William
Grossman, Jr. Second row: Henry Hamilton Hammer, Wallace Edgar Herrell, Joseph Martin Hitch, Jr.,
John Bohannan Hozier, Jr., Jethro Meriwether Hurt, Frederick Matthews Jacobs, William Roy Johnson,
Colman Carnegie Johnston, Robert Archer Goodwin Jones, Walter LeRoy Kilby, Edward Linden Kinney,
Gershon John Levin, Eleanor Holman McCoy, Hulburt Christopher McCoy Third row: Lewis Walke McIlhany,
Edgar Prentice McKinney, Roger Gregory Magruder, Charles Hampton Mauzy, Jr., Thomas Andrew
Moneymaker, Harold George Nix, Isaac Nathan Patterson, Asher Richardson Payne, Frederick Ralph
Person, Jack Berry Porterfield, Charles Walton Purcell, William Alexander Read Fourth row: Charles
Wolfe Rieber, William Randolph Robins, Jr., John Adrian Sims, John Thompson Brown Strode, John A.
Moorman Thompson, George Nathaniel Thrift, John Watkins Trenis, Robert Irvine Trent, Randolph Beaton
Turnbull, Algernon Keeling Turner, Vernon Atwill Turner, Wat Henry Tyler Fifth row: Ernest Thomas
Upson, John Ernest Vaughan, George Edward Waters, Herman Weinberg, Robert William White, Jr.,
William Hoge Wood, Jr.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168547/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168547</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168547/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
