<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2167343</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>Dr. Carl C. Speidel</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:created>1964-05</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>From the Medical Alumni News Letter, May 1964: "When Dr. Carl C. Speidel, Professor of
Anatomy at the University of Virginia School of Medicine, retires on June 30, he will end the
longest tenure of any member of the medical faculty,....forty-four years, with last thirty-three as
a full professor.... He is especially noted for the ingenuity with which he has used familiar
instruments -- the microscope and the movie camera -- to reveal important facts about cells. Because
he was the first to learn all the secrets of nerve growth by studying nerves inside animal
organisms, thus settling a scientific controversy that had lasted for seventy years, he received the
coveted $1,000 prize of the American Association for the Advancement of Science, given for 'a
notable contribution to science.' The presentation was made at the annual meeting of the
Association in New Orleans on January 1, 1932. Dr. Speidel was thirty-eight at the time, and had
just been made a full professor. Professor G. H. Parker of Harvard University, chairman of the
committee to select the winner, said: 'Dr. Speidel has proved once and for all that nerves do
not grow as a result of cells forming a chain, but that each nerve grows out of a single cell in a
central nervous system. This establishes the "outgrowth theory" of nerves as opposed to
the "chain theory."' No one had been able to check the out-growth on a living animal
before. Dr. Speidel started to study the development of the nerves by entirely novel methods, using
the dark-field illumination method to study nerves in the living animal. Instead of the light coming
from above the microscope, h e had the light come from the sides, resulting in better visibility.
Thus over a period of weeks he was able to see what nerves branch out from the spiral column and
spread, like the roots and branches of a plant, into all parts of the body. He found that nerves
went almost uncannily to the place they were intended for, and that they were quite sensitive to
their environment, with exploratory processes being continually sent out and retracted. His lighting
method also enabled him to see that a cut nerve cannot be spliced and made to function again,-- that
new nerve material must grow out from the root to repair the damage. Dr. Speidel's discovery
was heralded, not only in scientific journals, but as the 'lead' story on the front page
of the New York TIMES of January 2, 1932, with headlines proclaiming 'Dr. C. C. SPEIDEL WINS
SCIENCE PRIZE -- FINDS NERVE SECRETS SOUGHT FOR 70 YEARS: "CHAIN" THEORY IS UPSET --
Strands Are Found to Start from Single Cells and Explore Their Way Past Obstacles.' This was
big news, exciting news, in 1932. TIME Magazine featured Dr. Speidel's achievement as a major
scientific break-through, and in its issue of January 11, 1932 carried a story of his winning the A.
A. A. S. award with a typical TIME heading: 'Carl Caskey Speidel...looked into a tadpole's
tail.' This was one of many brilliant achievements which have brought honors and awards to Dr.
Speidel. His fields of original investigations have included experimental studies of nerve fibers,
sense organs, muscle fibers, hyperthyroidism, neuro-secretion, blood cells; effects of radiation
(X-Ray and ultraviolet) on cells; and microscopic movies of cell behavior (made directly from the
experimental animals).... Dr. Speidel was born on October 26, 1893 in Washington, D.C. He received
the Ph.B. degree from Lafayette College in 1914, and Ph.D. degree in biology from Princeton
University in 1918...."</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Health System</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Press coverage</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia. News Office</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2167343/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2167343</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2167343/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
