<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168552</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, First Year Class, 1930-1931</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Holsinger's Studio (Charlottesville, Va.)</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1930/1931</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>Class of 1934 Identified (L to R): First row: George Curtis Austin, Sullivan Gale Bedell,
George Simmerman Bourne, John Newton Bowden, Louis H. Bress, Alexander Gustavus Brown, Harry Paul
Browning, Charles Lorraine Cabell, George Robert Carpenter, Richard Reading Chamberlain, Hugh Tucker
Chelf, Jr.,Walter Franklin Cole, Robert Nelson Cooley, William Clark Cooper Second row: Thomas
Wallace Cox, Jr., Richard Earle DeButts, Margaret DeRonde, Julian Booth Doss, William Clegg
Eversole, Joseph Romeo Gentile, Joseph Edward Gladstone, Howard Clarke Glover, Noble Maxwell
Goodloe, John Bagby Haley, Walter Douglas Hankins, Harry H. Hardeen, George Alfred Hess, William
Rollan Hill Third row: Howard Thompson Holden, Clara Lucille Hoye, Joseph Leigh Hundley, John
Omohundro Hurt, William Allen Johns, William Virginius King, Jr., Israel Maurice Kruger, James F.
Lane, Armando Joseph Lauritano, Lewis Littlepage, Jr., John Fulton McGavock, Brooke Baylor Mallory,
James Calvin Martin, Lemuel Edward Mayo, Jr. Fourth row: William Perry Moore, Hugh Page Newbill,
Charles Collins Orr, Lawrence Pace, Roy Glenn Parks, Roy Randolph Powell, William Gilmer Puryear,
Mary Eleanor Rawls, John Walton Ross, Jr., Mack Irvin Shanholtz, James Robert Shanklin, Richard Vair
Shanklin, Jr., Richard Henry Smith, Charles L. Stinson Fifth row: Harry Benjamin Stone, Jr., William
Joshua Sturgis, Jr., Thomas William Tanner, John Hansford Thomas, Jr., William Edgar Waddell, Robert
Fletcher Watson, Harvie Lincoln Williams, Fletcher Johnston Wright, Jr.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168552/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168552</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168552/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
