<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168626</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, Fourth Year Class, 1946-1947</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Holsinger's Studio (Charlottesville, Va.)</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1946/1947</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>Back of photograph has signature of Dr. Mulholland. Class of 1947. Identified L to R: Front
row: Thomas Henry Alphin, Crescent Frank Balmenti, Hugh Miller Batson, Jr., John Bayard Britton,
Carl Ashton Broaddus, Jr., Robert Ludington Brown, III, William Knox Brown, Louis Herman Calisch,
Edmond Madison Chitwood, Jr., Herbert Augustine Claiborne, Jr., James Hicks Corey, Jr.. Second row:
Waverly Berkley Dashiell, Powell Garland Dillard, Jr., Ernest Malcolm Dixon, James Paul Elkins,
Nathaniel McGregor Ewell, Jr., Herbert Lyman Findley, Jr., Claiborne Willcox Fitchett, Jaime Higinio
Font, Edgar Coley Garrard, Billy Norris Golden, Robert Castleman Green, Jr., Stuart Leslie Haas.
Third row: Richard Littleton Haines, Eugene Augustus Hildreth, Edward Reginald Hipp, Jr., Charles
Edwin Horton, Eugene Rucker Johnson, James Barrett Jones, James Maurice Knopp, Henry Clayton Landon,
III, William Andrew MacIlwaine, John Houston McClung, Charles Theodore Michele. Fourth row: Joe
Elias Mitchell, Richard Allen Neubauer, Rea Blackwell Parker, Jr., Edwin Pearlman, James Andrew
Pettigrew, Murray Benjamin Pincus, Glenn Hickam Richmond, Frank Marcellus Ripberger, Guy Leslie
Rutledge, Cary Grayson Suter, Columbus Downing Tait. Fifth row: John Sheffield Tennant, Clyde
Hartwell Ward, Jr., Charles Warren Whitmore, James Dwight Whitt, Mortimer Lee Williams, David Cole
Wilson, Jr., Suzanne Hayward Worrilow, Alfred Yager.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168626/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168626</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168626/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
