<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168718</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, Fourth Year Class, 1967</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Thompson, Ralph R.</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1967</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>First row (l to r): Brian King, Paul Roy Yoder, John Rees Dunn, John Anthony Thomas, Donald
Barry Nolan, Charles Henry Emerson, Robert Lindsay Burger, Robert Stanley Brown, Washington Carlyle
Winn, Richard Thomas Edwards, III, Edgar Lambert Allport, David Michael Murphy, Joseph Franklin
Smiddy. Second row (l to r): Edward Blease Eadie, Jr., John Carl Spivey, Jr., James Sidney Smith,
Harold Prebble Settle, Jr., Roy Winston Lutz, Gordon Boyd Newell, Terrence Michael Murphy, Bonnie
Louis Reshefsky, Bruce McKinley Birch, Charles Arthur Whelan, Norman Louis Burak, William Joseph
Kagey, George Phillip Hillen, III, Robert Ray Henderson, Omer Lee Jeter, Jr. Third row (l to r):
Charles Samuel Betts, III, Vivian Winoma Pinn, Rick Allen Moore, RIchard Titus D'Alonzo, Walter
Lee King, William Wood Gough, Kenneth Edward Greer, Jeffrey Philip Robbins, Thomas Linwood Perry,
William Keath May, Thomas Eugene Boschen, Edward Gerald Abramson, Robert Eugene Searle, Allen Martin
Glasgow. Fourth row (l to r): Warden Hamlin Emory, Gordon Humphreys Smith, William Emory Cooley,
Jr., Louis Sutherland Allen, Jr., William Grier Kepler, Gary Calvert Jobin, James Ellis Dill, David
William Scott, III, Macdonald Dick, II, John Brantley Sydnor, Richard Hoppe Briggs, John Markle
Costenbader, Douglas Stephen Rowe, George Z. Seiters. Fifth row (l to r): Igor Magier, Samuel
Morgenstern LeBauer, Ernest Perry Buxton, III, Bryan Tighe Woods, John Lewis Starling, Henry
Claiborne Hawthorne, Jr., Thad Leroy Jones, George William Booze, David Rinser Bickers.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168718/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168718</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168718/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
