<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168641</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, Third Year Class, 1948-1949</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Holsinger's Studio (Charlottesville, Va.)</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1948/1949</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>First row (l to r): Charles Old Barclay, Jr., William Russell Brooks, George Allen Buckmaster,
Robert Sims Caldwell, James Campbell Cantrill, Floyd Wilson Carneal, Jr., John Baldwin Catlett,
James Colvin Causey, John Archibald Campbell Colston, Jr., Paul Tulane Craddock, Fred Seldon Cruser.
Second row (l to r): James Andrew DeLozier, Harrison Fertig, Robert Jerold Frank, Claude Robertson
Garfield, William Buhrman Garland, Jr., Lawrence Noah Gilliam, Warren Collins Gregory, Thomas Marion
Hall, Rozelle Hahn, Reginald Buchanan Henry, Jr., George William Herring. Third row (l to r): Seth
Guilford Hobart, Guy Foster Hollifield, James Morrison Hutcheson, Jr., Patricia Ann Lawrence,
Theodore Lather Marks, Paul Randall Marsh, Marion Dees Miller, Samuel Edmund Miller, Robert Edgar
Mitchell, Jr. Fourth row (l to r): Beryl Macy Oser, Gladys Pietri-Oms Sutherland, Rupert Wilson
Quaintance, Jr., Richard Eugene Rankin, Josiah Frederick Reed, Jr., James Cipriano Respess, Dorothy
Louella Reycroft, Benjamin Price Riley, Jr., John Kenneth Robertson, William Henry Romm. Fifth row
(l to r): Robert Louis Rowan, Roy Preston Sandidge, Jr., Edward Akira Sawada, Joseph Leon Schwartz,
Jr., Jose Anibal Semidey, Elmer Oswald Smith, Jr., Russell Smith, David Valentine Strider, Frank
Eugene Taylor, Bruce Edward Toppin, Clarence Brock Trower, Jr. Sixth row (l to r): Glenn Brady
Updike, Jr., Charles William Wagner, James Mounts Wolcott, Jr., James Burnley Wood, William Geoffrey
Wysor, Jr.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168641/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168641</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168641/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
