<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd"
    type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu dplava.xsd">
    <dcterms:identifier>uva-lib:2168684</dcterms:identifier>
    <dcterms:title>School of Medicine, Fourth Year Class, 1958-1959</dcterms:title>
    <dcterms:provenance>University of Virginia Library</dcterms:provenance>
    <dcterms:creator>Thompson, Ralph R.</dcterms:creator>
    <dcterms:created>1958/1959</dcterms:created>
    <dcterms:description>First row (l to r): Harold Lee Riley III, Frederic Aroyce Berry, Jr., Antonina Lidija Skapars,
Inta Ilse Janners Ertel, Garry Arnold Goldstein, James Douglas Deacon, Mervyn Robert King, William
Edward Daley, Leo Darrell Lagasse, Wilson Baxter Rumble, Abraham Isaac Sobel, Samir Mustafa Khalidy,
John William Bolen, Russell Austin Enke, Kenneth Robert McIntire. Second row (l to r): Rosa
Christiane Ogle, Charles Edwin Hess, Martha Alma Carpenter, Paul Yount Ertel, John Gusdon, Jr.,
Bertram Lee Warren, Alan Edward Siegal, Julian Dantzler Kelly, Frederick Bruce Forward, John Wise
Wescott, Robert Nelson Page, Jr., John Peyton Snead IV, Carter Snow Bagley, William Robert Wiseman.
Third row (l to r): Bernard Fruchtman, Stanton Peelle Nolan, William Markley McKinney, Niles Person
Severin, Rudi Ansbacher, Richard Joseph Duma, George Henry Guy, Mitchel Joe Dreese, Charles Little
Echols, David Stewart Summers, Albert Ayerst Carr, David Elijah Robinette, William Ford McKee, Jr.,
Gary Richard Vart. Fourth rwo (l to r): George Edward Shissler, David Phlegar Olinger, William
Blaine Kingree, Hadden Christopher Alexander, Joseph Raymond Barry Hutchinson, Jr., John Baggarly
Myers, William Sams Tunner, Samuel Frederick Brunk, Charles Chapman Binford, Henry Steele Lewis,
Jr., Waller Crockett Tabb, John David Fletcher, Roger Arthur Glover, Jr. Fifth row (l to r): John
Mathews Pitma, Jr., Jack Everett Arrants, David Lawrence Sagman, Matthew James McDermott, Jr.,
Walter Merritt Moore III, Frank Joseph O'Connor, Jr., Vincent Taormina, Robert Henry Bowden,
Jr., Douglas Kenley Armbrister, Roby Calvin Thompson, Jr., William Ford McKee, Jr., Laurence Lee
Cockerille, Jr., Sheldon David Glass.</dcterms:description>
    <dcterms:medium>nonprojected graphic</dcterms:medium>
    <dcterms:subject>Faculty</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>Students</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:subject>University of Virginia</dcterms:subject>
    <dcterms:type>Image</dcterms:type>
    <dcterms:spatial>United States</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Virginia</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:spatial>Charlottesville</dcterms:spatial>
    <dcterms:isPartOf>University of Virginia Visual History Collection</dcterms:isPartOf>
    <edm:hasType>black-and-white photographs</edm:hasType>
    <dcterms:isReferencedBy>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168684/iiif/manifest.json</dcterms:isReferencedBy>
    <dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/CNE/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
    <edm:isShownAt>http://search.lib.virginia.edu/catalog/uva-lib:2168684</edm:isShownAt>
    <edm:preview>https://iiif.lib.virginia.edu/iiif/uva-lib:2168684/full/!300,300/0/default.jpg</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
